{
    "id": "869e51dfc7ca4114807db336057a1eb9",
    "title": "Articles Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I was born in …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "May",
                "the May",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "44dd149f93a847e497d3db3d410f1509"
        },
        {
            "question": "My brother lives in …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Mumbai",
                "the Mumbai",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6ec5abf5ffbe458dbe63f9ce376a5121"
        },
        {
            "question": "We watched …………….. yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "movie",
                "a movie",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3306e42facc4458eb8158a31b01e4c04"
        },
        {
            "question": "Festivals are …………………. to celebrate.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "occasion",
                "an occasion",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "062a4e03365c460db76e1fab76589009"
        },
        {
            "question": "When ……………… sets, darkness descends.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sun",
                "the sun",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4ab18cdb7e7b4a50aa312ece6acc3eb5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The birds were pecking at ………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tree",
                "the tree",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fdd479f424bc4f7e9e84eace091c0a00"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will never forget your acts of ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "kindness",
                "the kindness",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dd55185c16a546939c63060d84abe4ca"
        },
        {
            "question": "Milk is the best food for ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "baby",
                "a baby",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "95fd3504c6564701a8330bd0cd907139"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. arrived on time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Train",
                "The train",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b00796c22cc74914a1b193453717c742"
        },
        {
            "question": "Give me ……………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pen",
                "a pen",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c6ee163fdcb84b7db84c124813a694b3"
        }
    ]
}